{
    "subject": "resource/Collier_Memorial_State_Park",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Klamath_County,_Oregon",
    "human_readable": "Collier Memorial State Park is located in Klamath County, Oregon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9768837094306946,
            "question": "In Klamath County, where can you find Collier Memorial State Park?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9767530560493469,
            "question": "Is Collier Memorial State Park located in Oregon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.933337926864624,
            "question": "In which state is Collier Memorial State Park situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9294087290763855,
            "question": "Where is Collier Memorial State Park located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.91265469789505,
            "question": "Which county contains Collier Memorial State Park?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8234997391700745,
            "question": "What is the county associated with Collier Memorial State Park?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8129207491874695,
            "question": "Can you identify the location of Collier Memorial State Park?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7927339673042297,
            "question": "What county does Collier Memorial State Park belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7396067380905151,
            "question": "What is the name of the state where Collier Memorial State Park resides?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7349843978881836,
            "question": "To what state does Collier Memorial State Park belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Collier Memorial State Park is located in Klamath County, Oregon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2712_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the state where Collier Memorial State Park resides?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2712_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What county does Collier Memorial State Park belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2712_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you identify the location of Collier Memorial State Park?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2712_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2712_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2712_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2712_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2712_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2712_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2712_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2712_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2712_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2712_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2712_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Collier Memorial State Park is indeed located in Klamath County, Oregon."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Collier Memorial State Park is situated in Klamath County, Oregon. Therefore, the statement \"Collier Memorial State Park is located in Klamath County, Oregon\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}